treksplorer.com 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy – Treksplorer

## Introduction

This privacy policy (“Policy”) and this site’s Terms of Service (together the “Terms”) govern all use of http://www.treksplorer.com and that site’s services (together the “Site” or “Services”). The owners and contributors to the Site will be referred to as “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Policy. By using the Site or its Services, and/or by clicking anywhere on this Site to agree to the Terms and this Policy, you are deemed to be a “user” for purposes of this Policy. You and every other user (“you” or “User” as applicable) are subject to this Policy. You and each user also agree to the Terms by using the Services. In these Terms, the word “Site” includes the site referenced above, its owner(s), contributors, suppliers, licensors, and other related parties.

We provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices, so that you can decide whether and how to interact with the Site and the Services.

We may release your information when we deem it appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Please also review our Terms of Use section that governs the use and the users of the Site.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If we have your email address, we may also send an email notifying you of any changes.

## Contact Data and Other Identifiable Information

This site collects certain user information, which may include a username and password, contact information, or any other data that you type in to the site. It may also identify your IP address to help identify you on future visits to the site. At our discretion, the Site may use this data to:

  * Personalize the user experience and/or customer service
  * Improve the site
  * To process transactions
  * Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature or function
  * Send email to users

## Mobile Device Privacy

The following applies to our site, when viewed on a mobile device:  
When accessed with a mobile device, our site may collect information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you have, device identifiers, and information about your use of the site. Regardless of the device you use to access the site, it will also collect information you provide, as well as information about your interaction with the site and its content.  
If location services are activated on your mobile device, our site may collect information about the location of your device. Your mobile network service providers may collect device-specific information, such as a device identifier, when you use our website or one of our mobile applications. This information collected by your mobile network service will not be associated with your user account with us, or with your personally identifiable information.

## Advertising Network

We use one or more third party vendors to serve ads on the Site. To serve ads and determine how our users use the Site, these services use cookies, or small pieces of code to serve ads to Site users based on users’ visits to the Site and others. Users may adjust their browser settings to disallow the use of cookies. With cookies turned off, certain features of the Site may work less efficiently or not at all.

We use Google as an advertising services provider for the Site. Users may opt out of Google’s use of the DART use-tracking cookie by visiting the Google advertising Policies & Principles page. If you opt out of ad tailoring, you will still see ads, but they will not be based on your browsing history, and they may appear in other languages.

## Disputes

We are based in Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, and you are contracting to use our Site. This Policy and all matters arising from your use of the Site are governed by and will be construed according to the laws of Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, without regard to any choice of laws rules of any jurisdiction. The federal courts and provincial courts that have geographical jurisdiction over disputes arising at our office location in Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, will be the only permissible venues for any and all disputes arising out of or in connection with this Policy or the Site and Service.

## ARBITRATION

Notwithstanding anything that may be contrary within the “Disputes” provisions above, all matters, and all claims within a multi-claim matter, that are arbitrable, including all claims for monetary damages, shall be decided by a single arbitrator to be selected by us, who shall hold hearings in or near Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, under the rules of International Centre for Dispute Resolution Canada.

## Terms Contact

If you have any questions about these Terms, please address them to info@treksplorer.com.

## Last Updated

These terms were last updated on  _September 19th, 2016._
